# **CAO DUC ANH - Mobile developer**

Thu Duc City, HCM City

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced and dedicated mobile app developer offering more than 8 years of expertise to the IT industry. Dynamic and personable with strong focus on application lifecycle. Strengths in Android native development and cross-platform mobile development with React Native.

### **SKILLS**

- Programming:
  - Android (Kotlin/Java 3 years)
  - React Native (Javascript 3 years)
  - IOS (Swift/Objective C 2 years)
  - Flutter (1 year)
  - C/C++ (2 years)
- Tools and Frameworks:
  - Git, SVN
  - Sketch, Zeplin, Figma, Marvelapp, Photoshop
  - Confluence, Jira

#### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

#### **SMARTPAY**

Mobile developer 5/2021- 12/2023

• Developed e-wallet application in react native (Ví SmartPay).

- Built functions: QR payment, transaction history, loan, withdraw money from FE Credit card, increase income for merchants...
- Used technical: Redux-Saga, React Navigation, Apisauce, React Native Firebase, Native module, Class component,
  React hooks
- Developed card payment application in Kotlin for POS device (SmartPOS).
  - Built functions: installment, insurance, link order, config White Label app, OPOS...
  - Used technical: MVVM, MVP, Dagger, Coroutines, Retrofit, Databinding, Live data, MQTT
- Developed android libraries for SmartPay (Android SDK).
  - SDK: Fema SDK Java, Merchant Locator Kotlin
  - Published SDKs to Github

#### **TMA SOLUTIONS**

Mobile developer 12/2020- 5/2021

- Developed and maintenance map application (Java/Objective C).
  - Used Adapter Design Pattern
  - Used map framework of customer
  - Checked for memory leaks on Android
- Performed assigned tasks: report, design, code, unit test.
- Worked with Japanese customers

### **VIETNAM INTERNATIONAL BANK**

Mobile developer 10/2018- 4/2020

- Developed mobile banking application in Java/Objective C (My VIB).
  - Built functions: Reward, Saving, Change UI, Prudential...
  - Used technical: Realm database, Rest APIs, Retrofit
- Developed SmartSale app in react native.
  - Built functions: source code structure, login, interest rates, notification...
  - Used technical: Redux-Saga, React Navigation, Apisauce, React Native Firebase, React Native SSL Pinning
  - Deployed app to TestFlight

### **NEWSTEAD TECHNOLOGIES VIET NAM**

Mobile developer 7/2017- 10/2018

- Developed application for restaurant (NuPOS Swift/Kotlin).
  - Created new app for iphone and android from app of Ipad
  - Built functions: Activities, Serve...
  - Used technical: MVC, Firebase, SQLite, Retrofit, Printer, Socket
- Developed application for bar (Ione Bottle app Kotlin).
  - Functions involved: Checkin, Checkout
  - Used technical: Retrofit, Rx Java, Camera

#### **FPT SOFTWARE HCM**

Software developer 10/2014- 3/2017

- Developed and maintenance application for ultrasound machines (C/C++/MFC).
- Analyzed the requirement, design, code, unit test, maintenance, report.
- Worked with Japanese customers.
- Worked with ISO process.

### **PROFESSIONAL PROJECTS**

- Flutter project: Watch Ads, Random Everything
  - Created new app in Flutter
  - Used technical: firebase message, google admob, provider, drawer, widget
  - Published app to Google Play Store
- PHP Website project: NITRA Collection of Mar
  - Published to Ubuntu server on AWS-EC2:

#### **EDUCATION**

# UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCES - HCM Major in Information Technology

2010-2014

- Programming languages: C++, C#, Java,
  HTML, XML, Android, Windows phone
- Databases: MS SQL, MySQL, SQLite
- Software Analysis and Design
- Object oriented programming, design pattern
- Data structure and algorithms

## **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**

I am a hard-working, detail-oriented, and careful person, always eager to learn and absorb new knowledge. I am ready to face challenges in work with a high level of determination. I am confident in my ability to make meaningful contributions in any work environment.